# Jason Gomes

**SOC** Analyst

Cyber Security Analyst with proficient and thorough experience and a good understanding of information technology. Specialized in proactive network monitoring of SIEM (Seceon). Have a deep knowledge of identifying and analyzing suspicious events. Able to use various security tools to perform logs and packet analysis.

#### Contact

#### **Address**

Margao, Goa, 403602

#### **Phone**

+91-9823817424

#### E-mail

jason140294@gmail.com

#### **Skills**

- Setting up of Windows/Linux workstations.
- Handling Networking and Organizational Networks. Wired, Wireless, and Fiber-Optic
- ♣ TCP-IP protocols
- Kali Linux Tools
- Network Pentest
- ♣ Incident Response
- ♣ Knowledge of ISO 27001

# **Work History**

2020-03 -2021-12

## **SOC Analyst**

ClouDDfn Pvt Ltd

- Conducted research & stayed updated on IT security trends & news to develop company-wide best practices
- Monitored organization's networks for security breaches and investigated violations
- Performed network-level penetration testing on network systems
- Providing technical support to clients on misconfigured applications.

2017-12 -2019-01

#### **IT Associate**

Taj Exotica Resort & Spa

- Attended guest calls and resolved device issues (Laptop & mobile) Configured and maintained network devices around the property
- Assisted in-house employees with computer system issues and network problems.

2017-10 -

## **Resident support Engineer**

2017-12 Stallion IT Solutions & Services

 Troubleshooting system issues relating to network and repairing corrupt &misconfigured software.

2017-03 -2017-10

## **Desktop Support Engineer**

Online Productivity Solutions Private Ltd

- Troubleshoot, resolve problems with server and client software through remote desktop support (TeamViewer, AmmyAdmin)
- Taking system image backup of systems
- Troubleshooting in-house internet issues
- Backups of clients' servers (Live website code & database).

#### **Education**

2021-07 - Master's Program
20211 AptWak Cybersocurity

AntWak Cybersecurity - Bangalore Credential ID: AW21CS02015

B.E: Computer Engineering

2011-06 -2015-06

Don Bosco College of Engineering - Goa University - Margao

# **Accomplishments**

- Developed a project for Railway Management
   System using Visual Basic in Visual Studio and
- Microsoft Access (Course project for Software Analysis & Design (SAD))
- Developed a project for Banking System using Visual Basic in Visual Studio and Oracle XE(Course project for Database Management System (DBMS))
- Developed a project "Guilty Agent Finder-To Capture the Agent Responsible for Data leakage" (Final Year Project).

## **Certifications**

- Cisco Certified Network Associate (Routing & Switching) [Validation ID:1388051216]
- Certified Information Security and Ethical Hacking (CISEH).
- Ethical Hacking Course (CEH by EC-Council). [ID: ECC2659084317]
- OSCP [Pursuing]